[Pronouns.page
=============](https://en.pronouns.page/)[Pronouns](https://en.pronouns.page/pronouns)[Dictionary](https://en.pronouns.page/dictionary)[Sources](https://en.pronouns.page/sources)[References](https://en.pronouns.page/links)[Blog](https://en.pronouns.page/blog)[Community](https://en.pronouns.page/terminology)[Contact](https://en.pronouns.page/contact)[Account](https://en.pronouns.page/account)

English

[Pronouns.page
=============](https://en.pronouns.page/)

English

Privacy Policy
--------------

_Last Updated: 2024-03-03 (Sentry)_

This Privacy Policy describes how the Service provided on the website **pronouns.page** and related subdomains and domains manages your personal data. The Service is operated by the “Neutral Language Council” collective and Nero Network (NL, KVK 88409120) who can be contacted via email: [contact@pronouns.page](mailto:contact@pronouns.page).

We make every effort to store your data securely and to ensure that any non-public data we store are not seized by or transferred to any third party, except those trusted parties described below.

Other than the data that you explicitly post on the Service as Content or share with us implicitly (eg. OAuth access tokens, if you use social login options), no additional private data connected to your account is being stored or processed by the Service.

You may edit or remove any Content you have posted on the Service.

When you contact us by email we store your email address in order to answer you and to ask you follow-up questions.

We only use first-party cookies and local storage to keep you logged in and save your preferences.

We use **Plausible** to analyse traffic on the website. Such data has no relation to your username, and your IP is anonymised. You can read their privacy policy [**here**](https://plausible.io/privacy).

We use **Cloudflare Turnstile** to filter out bots and prevent attacks. You can read their privacy policy [**here**](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy).

We use **Sentry** to monitor for errors and performance issues. The transmitted data has no relation to your username, unless it is contained inside the visited URL, and your IP is not stored.

In order to fund the project we show ads using third party vendors, including **Publift**, whose privacy policy is available [here](https://www.publift.com/privacy-policy). It uses cookies that enable it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites. You may opt out of personalised advertising by not giving your consent when prompted by clicking this link: We use **Google Tag Manager** to analyse traffic on the website. Such data has no relation to your username. You can read their privacy policy [**here**](https://support.google.com/tagmanager/answer/9323295).

Logs and backups are stored for no longer than 18 months.

Your personal data are protected by the GDPR, which means you have the right to see, correct, update and remove the data we store about you.

Authors of the website:

    We are a queer collective dedicated to assembling, researching, shaping and promoting gender neutral and nonbinary language. We also support actions towards equality and social justice.
* Kory [@kory\_warning](https://en.pronouns.page/@kory_warning)  
    translation, moderation, administration
* \- Juniper [@botanicalyhuman](https://en.pronouns.page/@botanicalyhuman)  
    Moderation, Bans, Terminology
* Avery (They/Them) [@realAvery](https://en.pronouns.page/@realAvery)  
    Moderation, Technical
* Paweł Dembowski [@ausir](https://en.pronouns.page/@ausir)  
    language, sources
* アンディ [@and.y](https://en.pronouns.page/@and.y)  
    Moderation, Sources, Reports
* Jacob [@Fishmael](https://en.pronouns.page/@Fishmael)  
    English, Russian, moderation
* Kevin [@kevinn](https://en.pronouns.page/@kevinn)  
    moderation, technical
* faera ☆ [@celestialflowers](https://en.pronouns.page/@celestialflowers)  
    moderation, english
* Asher [@jerryv](https://en.pronouns.page/@jerryv)  
    moderation
* Laker T. [@laker](https://en.pronouns.page/@laker)  
    Moderation, Sources
* Diego M. [@GreenWithin](https://en.pronouns.page/@GreenWithin)  
    English, Spanish (Español), Design, Translation, Moderation
* Torryn June 🌟 [@torrynjune](https://en.pronouns.page/@torrynjune)  
    German (Deutsch), administration, moderation, terminology, language, support
* Thomas Vos [@T\_Vos](https://en.pronouns.page/@T_Vos)  
    Project manager, User support, social media, English, Polish
* Szymon Misiek [@szymon](https://en.pronouns.page/@szymon)  
    language, sources
* tecc [@tecc](https://en.pronouns.page/@tecc)  
    programming, sysadmin, nitpicking
* Claudio Nicoli Pannacci [@kappanneo](https://en.pronouns.page/@kappanneo)  
    English, Swedish, Italian (work in progress), Upcoming language versions
* Benjamin [@therealbenpai](https://en.pronouns.page/@therealbenpai)  
    Moderation, Development, Community Programs, Support Services
* Andrea Vos [@andrea](https://en.pronouns.page/@andrea)  
    code, language, blog, project coordination, user support
* lucjan [@kaslucji](https://en.pronouns.page/@kaslucji)  
    moderation, terminology
* Wren [@wrac4242](https://en.pronouns.page/@wrac4242)  
    Moderation, Technical

Contact & social media:

* **Queer Calendar Bot:**
* **Merch:**

Contribute:

Light mode Automatic Dark mode

Version: [b37cbb79](https://gitlab.com/PronounsPage/PronounsPage/-/commit/b37cbb79ad730a0b1e1c037a7f1c14ed03afeefc) /

Legal:

* [Source code](https://gitlab.com/PronounsPage/PronounsPage) and content are licensed under [OQL](https://en.pronouns.page/license).
* Using [gradientmagic.com](https://www.gradientmagic.com/) and [Noto Color Emoji](https://fonts.google.com/noto/specimen/Noto+Color+Emoji)

Technical:

Sibling projects:

Stats:

**all language versions** | [only this version](#)

* Cards: **1.1M**
* Unique visitors: **145.1k** / month
* Page views: **872.8k** / month
* Currently online: **43**
* Registered users: **1M**

**We condemn war crimes.**  
Here's how you can help innocent people [in Ukraine](https://supportukrainenow.org/), [in Gaza](https://www.humanrightscareers.com/issues/charities-helping-civilians-in-palestine/) and [in other areas of military conflict](https://donate.unhcr.org/int/en/general).
